<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carl@carlschwan.eu>
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Claudio Cambra <claudio.cambra@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  -->
  <id>org.kde.merkuro.mail</id>
  <extends>org.kde.merkuro</extends>
  <name>Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">بريد ميركورو</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Електронна поща Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Correu de Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Correo de Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">דוא״ל Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">मेरकुरो मेल</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Merkuro Posta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Merkuro 메일</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Merkuro pasts</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Merkuro e-mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Poczta Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">E-Mail do Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Почта Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">बुध मेल</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Merkuro pošta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Merkuro e-post</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">மெற்குரோ அஞ்சல்</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Merkuro Posta</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Пошта Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro Mailxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Merkuro 郵件</name>
  <summary>Read and write emails</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">قراءة وكتابة البريد الإلكتروني</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Четене и писане на имейли</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Llegiu i escriviu correus electrònics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Llegiu i escriviu correus electrònics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Legi kaj skribi retpoŝtojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Leer y escribir correo electrónico</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">E-postak irakurri eta idatzi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Lire et écrire des courriels</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Lea e escriba por correo.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">קריאה וכתיבה של הודעות דוא״ל</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Lege e Scribe epostas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Leggi e scrivi messaggi di posta elettronica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">წაიკითხეთ და დაწერეთ ელფოსტა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Lezen en schrijven van e-mails</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Branje in pisanje elektronske pošte</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Läs och skriv e-post</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">E-postalarınızı okuyun ve yenilerini oluşturun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Читання і написання повідомлень електронної пошти</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxRead and write emailsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">閱讀或撰寫電子郵件</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Merkuro Mail is a free and open source email client. Merkuro Mail is part of the Merkuro groupware suite and is currently in beta. For now, it only allows you to read your emails.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">بريد ميركورو هو عميل بريد إلكتروني مجاني ومفتوح المصدر. يعد بريد ميركورو جزءًا من مجموعة برامج ميركورو للمجموعات وهو حاليًا في مرحلة تجريبية. في الوقت الحالي، يسمح لك فقط بقراءة رسائل البريد الإلكتروني الخاصة بك.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Merkuro Mail е безплатен имейл клиент с отворен код. Merkuro Mail е част от груповия пакет Merkuro и в момента е в бета версия. Засега ви позволява само да четете имейлите си.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Merkuro Mail és un client de correu electrònic gratuït i de codi obert. El Merkuro Mail forma part de la suite de treball en grup Merkuro i actualment es troba en beta. De moment, només permet llegir els vostres correus electrònics.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Correu de Merkuro és un client de correu electrònic gratuït i de codi obert. El Correu de Merkuro forma part de la suite de treball en grup Merkuro i actualment es troba en beta. De moment, només permet llegir els vostres correus electrònics.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Merkuro Mail er den frie og åben-kildekode e-mail-klient. Merkuro Mail er en del af Merkuro groupware-sættet og er lige nu i beta. Lige nu kan du kun læse dine e-mails.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Merkuro Mail is a free and open source email client. Merkuro Mail is part of the Merkuro groupware suite and is currently in beta. For now, it only allows you to read your emails.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Merkuro Mail estas libera kaj malfermfonta retpoŝta kliento. Merkuro Mail estas parto de la Merkuro grupvaro-serio kaj estas nuntempe en beta. Aktuale, ĝi nur permesas vin legi viajn retpoŝtojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Correo de Merkuro es un cliente de correo electrónico libre y de código abierto. Correo de Merkuro forma parte del paquete de software colaborativo Merkuro, que está en fase beta en la actualidad. Por ahora, solo le permite leer su correo electrónico.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«Merkuro Mail» sorburu irekiko e-posta bezero aske bat da. «Merkuro Mail» «Merkuro» talde-lanerako aplikazio multzoaren atal bat da eta une honetan beta egoeran dago. Oraingoz, e-postak irakurtzen besterik ez dizu uzten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Merkuro-sähköposti on vapaa avoimen koodin sähköpostioohjelma. Se on osa Merkuro-työryhmäohjelmistoa ja on vielä beetaa. Toistaiseksi sillä voi vain lukea sähköpostit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le logiciel Merkuro Mail est un client de messagerie gratuit et « Open source ». Il fait partie de la suite Merkuro de logiciels de groupe de travail. Il est actuellement en version « Bêta ». Pour l'instant, il ne vous permet que de lire vos courriels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Merkuro Mail é un cliente de correo libre e de balde que forma parte da colección de programas de traballo en equipo Merkuro, e está en fase de probas. De momento só permite ler o correo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">דוא״ל Merkuro הוא לקוח דוא״ל חופשי ובקוד פתוח. דוא״ל Merkuro הוא חלק מחבילת כלי שיתוף הפעולה והוא כרגע בשלבי ניסוי. לבינתיים הוא רק מאפשר לקרוא הודעות דוא״ל.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">मेरकुरो मेल एक मुक्त और खुला स्रोत ईमेल क्लाइंट है। मेरकुरो मेल मेरकुरो मेरकुरो अनुप्रयोग समूह का हिस्सा है और वर्तमान में बीटा में है। अभी के लिए, यह आपको केवल अपने ईमेल पढ़ने में सहायक है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Merkuro Mail egy szabad és nyílt forráskódú e-mail kliens. A Merkuro csoportmunka csomag része, jelenleg béta állapotú. Egyelőre csak az e-mailek olvasását teszi lehetővé.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Merkuro es un cliente de e-posta a fonte aperite e libere. Merkuro Mail es parte de suite de gruppo Merkuro e es currentemente in beta. Per nunc, illo te permitte solmente leger tu messages de e-posta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Merkuro Posta è un client di posta elettronica libero e open source. Merkuro Posta fa parte della suite di groupware Merkuro ed è attualmente in versione beta. Per ora, ti consente solo di leggere i tuoi messaggi di posta elettronica.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Merkuro Mail-ი უფასო და ღია კოდის მქონე ელფოსტის კლიენტია. Merkuro Mail-ი Merkuro Groupware-ის ნაწილს წარმოადგენს და ამჟამად ბეტა მდგომარეობაშია. ახლა მას მხოლოდ თქვენი ელფოსტების წაკითხვა შეუძლია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Merkuro 메일은 자유 오픈 소스 이메일 클라이언트입니다. Merkuro 메일은 Merkuro 그룹웨어 제품군의 일부분이며 현재 베타 상태입니다. 현재 이메일 읽기만 가능합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Merkuro“ pasts ir brīvs un atvērtā koda e-pasta klients. „Merkuro“ pasts ir daļa no „Merkuro“ programmatūras un šobrīd ir beta izstrādes stadijā. Šobrīd tas ļauj tikai lasīt e-pasta vēstules.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro Mail is een vrije en open-source e-mailclient. Merkuro Mail is onderdeel van de suite Merkuro groepsware en is nu in beta. Op dit moment biedt het u alleen het lezen van uw e-mails.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Poczta Merkuro to darmowy i o otwartym kodzie program pocztowy. Poczta Merkuro jest częścią zestawu programów do pracy grupowej i jej obecna jakość to beta. Obecnie pozwala tylko na odczyt wiadomości.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Merkuro Mail é um cliente de e-mail gratuito e de código aberto. Merkuro Mail faz parte do pacote do software colaborativo Merkuro e está atualmente em versão beta. Por enquanto, só permite que você leia seus e-mails.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Почта Merkuro — свободная программа с открытым исходным кодом, предназначенная для работы с электронной почтой. Почта Merkuro входит в набор программ Merkuro для групповой работы и в настоящее время представляет собой бета-версию. Пока поддерживается только чтение писем.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">Merkuro Mail एकः निःशुल्कः मुक्तस्रोतः च ईमेलग्राहकः अस्ति । Merkuro Mail Merkuro groupware suite इत्यस्य भागः अस्ति, सम्प्रति बीटा इत्यस्मिन् अस्ति । इदानीं कृते केवलं भवतः ईमेल-पत्राणि पठितुं शक्यते ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Merkuro Mail je prosti in odprtokodni e-poštni odjemalec. Merkuro Mail je del zbirke Merkuro skupinske programske opreme in je trenutno v beta različici. Za zdaj vam omogoča le branje vaše e-pošte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Merkuro e-post är ett fritt e-postprogram med öppen källkod. Merkuro e-post ingår i Merkuro grupprogramsviten och är för närvarande beta. För tillfället låter det dig bara läsa din e-post.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Merkuro Posta, ücretsiz ve açık kaynaklı bir e-posta istemcisidir. Merkuro Posta, Merkuro yazılım grubunun bir parçasıdır ve sınama aşamasındadır. Şu anda yalnızca e-postalarınızı okumanıza izin verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Пошта Merkuro є вільним клієнтом електронної пошти з відкритим кодом. Пошта Merkuro є частиною комплексу програм для групової роботи Merkuro. Зараз програма перебуває на етапі тестування. Поточна версія надає вам змогу лише читати ваші повідомлення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro Mail is a free and open source email client. Merkuro Mail is part of the Merkuro groupware suite and is currently in beta. For now, it only allows you to read your emails.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Merkuro 郵件是一個自由開源的電子郵件程式。Merkuro 郵件是 Merkuro 群組套裝軟體的一部分，目前仍在 Beta 測試階段而只能讓您閱讀您的電子郵件。</p>
  </description>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <provides>
    <binary>merkuro-mail</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/merkuro.mail/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=merkuro</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24"/>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20"/>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05"/>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08"/>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03"/>
    <release version="22.08.2" date="2022-10-13"/>
    <release version="22.08.1" date="2022-09-08"/>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/merkuro/mail.png</image>
      <caption>Mail View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض البريد</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Изглед на електронна поща</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de correu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de correu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Mailvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Mail View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Poŝtperspektivo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de correo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Posta ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Viestinäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en courriels</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de correo.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת דוא״ל</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">मेल दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Levélnézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Posta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista messaggi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">ელფოსტის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">메일 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Pasta skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">E-mailweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok poczty</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização de e-mail</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр почты</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">मेल व्यू</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie pošty</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled pošte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">E-postvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ta">அஞ்சல் காட்சி</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Posta Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд пошти</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMail Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">電子郵件檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#merkuro:kde.org</value>
    <value key="KDE::mastodon">https://kde.social/@merkuro</value>
    <value key="KDE::supporters">manchicken</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.merkuro.mail.desktop</launchable>
</component>
