<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carl@carlschwan.eu>
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Claudio Cambra <claudio.cambra@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  -->
  <id>org.kde.merkuro.calendar</id>
  <name>Merkuro Calendar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Calendari del Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Calendari de Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Calendario de Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Merkuro-agenda</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Calendário do Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Erdenay Takvim</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Календар Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro Calendarxx</name>
  <summary>Manage your tasks and events with speed and ease</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestioneu les tasques i esdeveniments amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestioneu les tasques i esdeveniments amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestión de tareas y eventos con rapidez y facilidad</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gérer vos tâches et vos évènements avec efficacité et facilité</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Uw taken en afspraken beheren met snelheid en gemak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Faça a gestão das suas tarefas e eventos rápida e facilmente</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Görevlerinizi ve etkinliklerinizi hızlıca ve kolayca yönetin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Швидко і ефективно керуйте вашими записами завдань і подій</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxManage your tasks and events with speed and easexx</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community, Clau Cambra and Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Comunitat KDE, Clau Cambra i Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Comunitat KDE, Clau Cambra i Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">La Comunidad KDE, Clau Cambra y Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Communauté KDE, Clau Cambra et Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE-gemeenschap, Clau Cambra en Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Comunidade do KDE, Clau Cambra e Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu, Clau Cambra ve Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE, Clau Cambra і Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Community, Clau Cambra and Carl Schwanxx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Merkuro Calendar is a calendar application that allows you to manage your tasks and events. Kalendar supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Calendari del Merkuro és una aplicació de calendari que permet gestionar les tasques i esdeveniments. Dona suport a dos calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Calendari de Merkuro és una aplicació de calendari que permet gestionar les tasques i esdeveniments. Dona suport a dos calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Calendario de Merkuro es una aplicación de calendario que permite la gestión de tareas y eventos. Kalendar permite usar calendarios locales y gran cantidad de calendarios en línea: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav y otros más.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro-agenda is een agenda-toepassing die u uw taken en afspraken laat beheren. Kalendar ondersteunt zowel lokale agenda's alsook een veelheid aan online agenda's: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav en vele anderen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Erdenay Takvim, görevlerinizi ve etkinliklerinizi yönetmenize izin veren bir takvim uygulamasıdır. Erdenay, hem yerel hem de birçok çevrimiçi takvimi destekler: Nextcloud, Google® Takvim, Outlook®, Caldav ve daha birçoğu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Календар Merkuro — програма-календар, за допомогою якої ви можете керувати вашими записами завдань і подій. У Kalendar передбачено підтримку локальних календарів, а також цілого спектру інтернет-календарів: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav та багатьох інших.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro Calendar is a calendar application that allows you to manage your tasks and events. Kalendar supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.xx</p>
    <p>Merkuro gives you many ways to interact with your events. The month view provides an overview of the entire month; the week view presents a detailed hour-by-hour overview of your week; and the schedule view lists all of your upcoming events so that you can easily and quickly plan ahead.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Merkuro ofereix moltes maneres d'interactuar amb els esdeveniments. La vista mensual proporciona una visió general de tot el mes. La vista setmanal presenta una visió general detallada de la vostra setmana. I la vista de llista enumera tots els pròxims esdeveniments de manera que pugueu planificar amb facilitat i rapidesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Merkuro oferix moltes maneres d'interactuar amb els esdeveniments. La vista mensual proporciona una visió general de tot el mes. La vista setmanal presenta una visió general detallada de la vostra setmana. I la vista de llista enumera tots els pròxims esdeveniments de manera que pugueu planificar amb facilitat i rapidesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Merkuro proporciona muchos modos de interactuar con eventos. La vista mensual proporciona un resumen de todo el mes. La vista semanal presenta un detallado resumen de la semana por horas. Y la vista de planificación lista todos los eventos futuros para que pueda hacer planes con antelación de forma fácil y rápida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro geeft u veel manieren om te werken met uw afspraken. De maandweergave biedt een overzicht over de gehele maand; de weekweergave presenteert een gedetailleerde uur-voor-uur overzicht van uw week; en de planningweergavelijsten al uw komende afspraken zodat u gemakkelijk en snel vooruit kunt plannen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Merkuro dá-lhe várias formas de interagir com os seus eventos. A área mensagel dá uma visão geral para o mês inteiro; a vista semanal apresenta uma visão detalhada, hora-a-hora, da sua sua semana; a vista de horário mostra todos os seus próximos eventos, de forma que consiga planear fácil e rapidamente os seus eventos no futuro.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Erdenay, size etkinliklerinizi yönetmek için birçok kolay yol sunar. Ay görünümü, tüm ayın genel görünümünü sağlarken hafta görünümü, haftanızın saat saat ayrıntılı bir bakışını sağlar. Ajanda görünümüyle tüm sıradaki etkinliklerinizi kolayca görebilir ve buna göre kolayca planlamanızı yapabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою Merkuro ви зможете працювати із вашими записами подій у багато способів. На панелі перегляду місяця буде показано загальний огляд подій місяця; на панелі перегляду тижня ви зможете побачити погодинних розклад подій тижня; а на панелі розкладу буде показано список усіх наступних подій, який надасть вам змогу без проблем швидко спланувати свої дії.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro gives you many ways to interact with your events. The month view provides an overview of the entire month; the week view presents a detailed hour-by-hour overview of your week; and the schedule view lists all of your upcoming events so that you can easily and quickly plan ahead.xx</p>
    <p>A tasks view is also available, making it possible for you to manage your tasks and subtasks with Merkuro's powerful tree view and its customisable filtering capabilities.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">També hi ha disponible una vista de tasques, la qual permet gestionar les tasques i subtasques amb la potent vista en arbre del Merkuro i les seves capacitats personalitzables de filtratge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">També hi ha disponible una vista de tasques, la qual permet gestionar les tasques i subtasques amb la potent vista en arbre de Merkuro i les seues capacitats personalitzables de filtratge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">También está disponible una vista de tareas, que posibilita la gestión de tareas y subtareas con la potente vista de árbol de Merkuro y sus flexibles capacidades de filtrado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een takenweergave is ook beschikbaar, waarmee u uw taken en subtaken met de krachtige boomstructuur weergave van Merkuro en zijn aanpasbare mogelijkheden voor filtering kunt beheren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Também está disponível uma área de tarefas, tornado possível para si a gestão das suas tarefas e sub-tarefas, com a árvore poderosa do Merkuro e as suas capacidades de filtragem personalizadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Ayrıca bir görevler görünümü kullanımınıza açıktır. Bununla tüm görevlerinizi ve ilişkin alt görevlerinizi Erdenay'ın güçlü ağaç görünümü ve özelleştirilebilir süzme yetenekleriyle kolayca yönetebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Також доступна панель перегляду завдань, за допомогою якої ви можете керувати записами завдань і підзавдань у потужній ієрархічній структурі записів Merkuro із гнучкими можливостями фільтрування.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxA tasks view is also available, making it possible for you to manage your tasks and subtasks with Merkuro's powerful tree view and its customisable filtering capabilities.xx</p>
    <p>Merkuro was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Merkuro s'ha construït amb la idea de ser usable a l'escriptori, al mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Merkuro s'ha construït amb la idea de ser utilitzable en l'escriptori, al mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Merkuro se creó con la idea de ser usable en el escritorio, en el móvil y en cualquier otra cosa entre ambos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro is gebouwd met het idee om bruikbaar te zijn op een bureaublad, op een mobiel en alles er tussenin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Merkuro foi criado com a possibilidade de ser usado no computador, nos dispositivos móveis e em tudo o que seja intermédio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Erdenay, hem masaüstü hem taşınabilir aygıtlar hem de ikisinin arasındaki her şey dikkate alınarak geliştirilmiştir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Merkuro побудовано так, що програмою можна користуватися на звичайному комп'ютері, на мобільному телефоні і на усіх проміжних пристроях.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.xx</p>
  </description>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/month_view.png</image>
      <caption>Month View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en mois</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Maandweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista Mensal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ay Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд місяця</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMonth Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/week_view.png</image>
      <caption>Week View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista semanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en semaines</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Weekweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista da Semana</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Hafta Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд тижня</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxWeek Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/schedule_view.png</image>
      <caption>Schedule View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la planificació</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la planificació</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de planificación</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en calendrier</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Planningsweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de Calendarização</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ajanda Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxSchedule Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/task_view.png</image>
      <caption>Task View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de tasques</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de tasques</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de tareas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en tâches</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Taakweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista das Tarefas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Görev Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд завдання</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTask Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/mobile_view.png</image>
      <caption>Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Móvil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Mobiel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Telemóvel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Taşınabilir</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мобільний</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMobilexx</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>merkuro-calendar</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/merkuro.calendar/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/pim/merkuro/-/issues</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20"/>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05"/>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08"/>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03"/>
    <release version="22.08.2" date="2022-10-13"/>
    <release version="22.08.1" date="2022-09-08"/>
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#merkuro:kde.org</value>
    <value key="KDE::mastodon">https://kde.social/@merkuro</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.merkuro.merkuro.desktop</launchable>
</component>
