<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carl@carlschwan.eu>
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Claudio Cambra <claudio.cambra@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  -->
  <id>org.kde.merkuro</id>
  <name>Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">ميركورو</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Merkuro Mail</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Merkuro</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuroxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Merkuro</name>
  <summary>Manage your tasks, events and contacts with speed and ease</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">أدر المهام والأحداث والمتراسلين بسرعة وسهولة</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Управлявайте вашите задачи, събития и контакти с бързина и лекота</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestioneu les tasques, els esdeveniments i els contactes amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestioneu les tasques, els esdeveniments i els contactes amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Spravujte své úkoly, události a kontakty rychle a jednoduše</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Adminstrér dine opgaver, begivenheder og kontaker nemt og hurtigt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Manage your tasks, events and contacts with speed and ease</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Mastrumu viajn taskojn, eventojn kaj kontaktojn rapide kaj facile</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestión rápida y fácil de tareas, eventos y contactos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Kudeatu zure zereginak, ekitakdiak eta kontaktuak azkar eta erraz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Hallitse tehtäviä, tapahtumia ja yhteystietoja nopeasti ja helposti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gérer vos tâches, vos évènements et vos contacts avec efficacité et facilité</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestione as súas tarefas, eventos e contactos de forma rápida e fácil.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">ניהול המשימות, האירועים ואנשי הקשר שלך במהירות ובקלות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Kezelje feladatait, eseményeit és névjegyeit gyorsan és könnyedén</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Gere tu cargas, eventos e contactos con velocitate e facilitate</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestisci le tue attività, gli eventi e i contatti con velocità e facilità</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">მართეთ თქვენი დავალებები, მოვლენები და კონტაქტები ერთად სწრაფად და იოლად</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Viegli un raiti pārvaldiet savus uzdevumus, notikumus un kontaktpersonas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Uw contacten, afspraken en contactpersonen beheren met snelheid en gemak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzaj swoimi zadaniami, wydarzeniami i kontaktami szybko i z łatwością</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerencie suas tarefas, compromissos e contatos com rapidez e facilidade</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljajte svoje naloge, dogodke in stike hitro in z lahkoto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hantera dina uppgifter, händelser och kontakter snabbt och enkelt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Yapılacaklarınızı, etkinliklerinizi ve kişilerinizi kolaylıkla yönetin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Швидко і ефективно керуйте вашими записами завдань, подій і контактів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxManage your tasks, events and contacts with speed and easexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">快速簡單地管理您的工作事項、活動事件以及聯絡人</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Merkuro is a calendar and contact application that allows you to manage your tasks, events and contacts. Merkuro supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar"> ميركورو هو تطبيق تقويم وجهات اتصال يتيح لك إدارة مهامك وأحداثك وجهات اتصالك. يدعم ميركورو التقويمات المحلية بالإضافة إلى العديد من التقويمات عبر الإنترنت: Nextcloud وGoogle® Calendar وOutlook® وCaldav وغير ذلك الكثير.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Merkuro е приложение за календар и контакти, което ви позволява да управлявате вашите задачи, събития и контакти. Той поддържа както локални календари, така и множество онлайн календари: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav и много други.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Merkuro és una aplicació de calendari i de contactes que permet gestionar les tasques, els esdeveniments i els contactes. El Merkuro admet calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Merkuro és una aplicació de calendari i de contactes que permet gestionar les tasques, els esdeveniments i els contactes. Merkuro admet calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Merkuro er et kalender- og kontaktprogram, der lader dig adminstrere dine opgaver, begivenheder og kontakter. Merkuro understøtter både lokale kalenedere og mange online koalendere: Nextcloud, Google® Kalender, Outlook®, Caldav og mange flere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Merkuro is a calendar and contact application that allows you to manage your tasks, events and contacts. Merkuro supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Merkuro estas kalendara kaj kontakta aplikaĵo kiu permesas al vi mastrumi viajn taskojn, eventojn kaj kontaktojn. Merkuro subtenas ambaŭ lokajn kalendarojn same kiel amason da interretaj kalendaroj: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav kaj multajn pli.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Merkuro es una aplicación de calendario y de contactos que le permite gestionar tareas, eventos y contactos. Merkuro permite usar calendarios locales y una gran variedad de calendarios en línea: Nextcloud, calendario de Google® y caldav de Outlook®, entre otros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Merkuro egutegi eta kontaktu aplikazio bat da, zure zereginak, ekitaldiak eta kontaktuak kudeatzeko aukera eskaintzen dizuna. Merkuro-k biak onartzen ditu, egutegi lokalak zein makina bat lerroko egutegi: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, eta beste asko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Merkuro on kalenteri- ja yhteystietosovellus, jolla hallita tehtäviä, tapahtumia ja yhteystietoja. Se tukee niin paikallisia kuin monia verkkokalentereitakin: Nextcloudia, Googlen® kalenteria, Outlookia®, CalDAVia ja monia muita.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Merkuro est une application d'agendas et de contacts, vous permettant de gérer vos tâches, vos évènements et vos contacts. Elle prend en charge les agendas locaux ainsi qu'une multitude d'agendas en ligne comme Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, CalDAV et bien d'autres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Merkuro é unha aplicación de calendarios e contactos que lle permite xestionar as tarefas, eventos e contactos. Merkuro permite tanto calendarios locais como varios calendarios por Internet: de Nextcloud, de Google Calendar, de Outlook, de Caldav e de máis servizos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Merkuro הוא יישום לוח שנה ואנשי קשר שמאפשר לך לנהל את המשימות,האירועים ואנשי הקשר שלך, Merkuro תומך בלוח שנה מקומי לרבות מגוון לוחות שנה מקוונים כגון: Nextcloud,‏ Google® Calendar,‏ Outlook®‎,‏ Caldav ועוד רבים וטובים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Merkuro egy naptár- és névjegyalkalmazás, amely lehetővé teszi feladatai, eseményei és névjegyeikezelését. Támogatja a helyi naptárakat és számos online naptárat: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, és sok-sok egyebet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Merkuro  es un application de calendario e contactos que te permitte gerer tu cargas, eventos e contactos. Merkuro supporta sia calendarios local que un multitude de calendarios in linea: Nextcloud,Google ® Calendar, Outlook ®, Caldav, e multe altere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Merkuro Calendario è un'applicazione per calendari e contatti che ti consente di gestire le tue attività, gli eventi e i contatti. Merkuro supporta sia i calendari locali che una moltitudine di calendari in linea: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav e molti altri.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Merkuro კალენდრის აპლიკაციაა, რომელიც თქვენი ამოცანებისა და მოვლენების მართვაში დაგეხმარებათ. Merkuro-ს ორივე, ლოკალური და ონლაინ კალენდარების მხარდაჭერა გააჩნია: NextCoud, Google Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav და სხვა.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Merkuro“ ir kalendārs un kontaktu programma, kas ļauj pārvaldīt uzdevumus, notikumus un kontaktpersonas. „Merkuro“ atbalsta gan lokālus kalendārus, gan arī daudzus tiešsaistes kalendārus: „Nextcloud“, „Google® Calendar“, „Outlook“®, „Caldav“ un daudzus citus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro is een toepassing voor agenda en contactpersonen die u uw taken en afspraken laat beheren. Merkuro ondersteunt zowel lokale agenda's alsook een veelheid aan online agenda's: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav en vele anderen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Merkuro jest aplikacją kalendarza i kontaktów, która umożliwia zarządzanie twoimi zadaniami, wydarzeniami i kontaktami. Merkuro obsługuje zarówno kalendarze lokalne, jak i wiele kalendarzy zdalnych: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i wiele innych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Merkuro é um aplicativo de calendário e contatos que permite gerenciar suas tarefas, compromissos e contatos. Merkuro oferece suporte a calendários locais e também a uma infinidade de calendários online: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav e muito mais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Merkuro je aplikacija za koledar in stike, ki vam omogoča upravljanje opravil, dogodkov in kontaktov. Merkuro podpira tako lokalne koledarje kot tudi številne spletne koledarje: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav in številne druge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Merkuro är ett kalenderprogram som tillåter dig att hantera dina uppgifter, händelser och kontakter. Merkuro stöder både lokala kalendrar samt en mängd nätkalendrar: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, och många fler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Merkuro, görevlerinizi, etkinliklerinizi ve kişilerinizi yönetmenizi sağlayan bir takvim ve iletişim uygulamasıdır. Merkuro, hem yerel takvimleri hem de çok sayıda çevrimiçi takvimi destekler: NextCloud, Google® Takvim, Outlook®, Caldav ve daha fazlası.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Merkuro — програма-календар, за допомогою якої ви можете керувати вашими записами завдань, подій і контактів. У Merkuro передбачено підтримку локальних календарів, а також цілого спектру інтернет-календарів: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav та багатьох інших.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro is a calendar and contact application that allows you to manage your tasks, events and contacts. Merkuro supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Merkuro 是一個行事曆與聯絡人應用程式，讓您管理您的工作事項、活動事件以及聯絡人。Merkuro 支援本地行事曆以及許多線上行事曆：Nextcloud、Google® Calendar、Outlook®、CalDAV 等等。</p>
    <p>Merkuro was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">صمم تقويم ميركورو بفكرة أن تكون قابل للاستخدام على سطح المكتب وعلى الهاتف المحمول وكل شيء بينهما.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Merkuro е създаден с идеята да може да се използва на на всякакви устройства: от  настолен компютър до мобилно устройство.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Merkuro s'ha construït amb la idea de ser usable a l'escriptori, al mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Merkuro s'ha construït amb la idea de ser utilitzable en l'escriptori, en el mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Merkuro blev bygget med idéen om at kunne bruges på desktop, på mobiler og alt derimellem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Merkuro wurde mit der Idee entworfen, auf jedem Gerät vom Desktop-PC bis zum Mobiltelefon benutzbar zu sein.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Merkuro was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Merkuro estis konstruita kun la ideo esti uzebla en labortablo, en poŝtelefono kaj ĉio intere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Merkuro se creó con la idea de poder usarlo en el escritorio, en dispositivos móviles y en cualquier formato entre ellos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Merkuro, mahaigainean, mugikorrean eta tarteko guztietan erabilia izateko ideiarekin eraiki da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Merkuro on luotu olemaan hyödyksi niin työpöydällä, mobiilissa kuin kaikkialla siltä väliltäkin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Merkuro a été conçu avec l'idée d'être utilisable sur un ordinateur de bureau, sur un téléphone portable et dans tous les périphériques intermédiaires.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Merkuro construíuse para poder usarse en calquera dispositivo, desde escritorios a móbiles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Merkuro נבנה מתוך רעיון לספק שירות במחשב, במכשיר הנייד ובתווך שביניהם.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Merkurot úgy tervezték, hogy használható legyen mindenféle eszközön, az asztali számítógépektől kezdve a mobiltelefonokig.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Merkuro esseva construite con le idea de esser usabile sur scriptorio, sur mobile e  toto in le medie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Merkuro è stato creato con l'idea di essere utilizzabile su desktop, mobile e tutto il resto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Merkuro აგებულია იდეით, რომ გამოყენებადი იყოს სამუშაო მაგიდაზე, მობილურზე და ყველაფერზე მათ შუა.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Merkuro는 데스크톱, 모바일, 그 사이에 있는 모든 것에서 편하게 사용할 수 있도록 개발되었습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Merkuro“ ir veidots, lai būtu ērti lietojams datorā, mobilās ierīcēs un visās ierīcēs pa vidu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Merkuro is gebouwd met het idee om bruikbaar te zijn op een bureaublad, op een mobiel en alles er tussenin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Merkuro został zbudowany z zamiarem bycia użytecznym na urządzeniach biurkowych, przenośnych i wszystkich innych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Merkuro foi construído com a ideia de ser utilizável em desktops, dispositivos móveis e outras plataformas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Merkuro je bil zgrajen z idejo, da bi ga lahko uporabljali na namizju, mobilniku in vsem vmes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Merkuro är byggd med idén att vara användbar på skrivbordsdatorer eller mobiler och allting däremellan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Merkuro masaüstünde, taşınabilir aygıtlarda ve aradaki her şeyde kullanılabilir olma düşüncesiyle yapıldı.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Merkuro побудовано так, що програмою можна користуватися на звичайному комп'ютері, на мобільному телефоні і на усіх проміжних пристроях.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMerkuro was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Merkuro 最初便以在桌面、行動裝置和所有其間的裝置上皆可使用為目標。</p>
  </description>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/merkuro/calendar-month.png</image>
      <caption>Month View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الشهر</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Месечен изглед</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na měsíc</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Månedvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Monatsansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Month View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Monata Vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Hilabeteko ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kuukausinäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en mois</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista mensual.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת חודש</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Havi nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de mense</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan Bulan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista mensile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">თვის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">월간 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Mēneša skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Maandweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok miesiąca</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização por mês</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Mesačný pohľad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Mesečni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Månadsvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ay Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд місяця</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMonth Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">月份檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/merkuro/contact.png</image>
      <caption>Contact list</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">قائمة المراسلين</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Списък с контакти</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Llista de contactes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Llista de contactes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Seznam kontaktů</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Kontaktliste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Contact list</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Kontaktlisto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Lista de contactos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kontaktu-zerrenda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Yhteystietoluettelo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Liste de contacts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Lista de contactos.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">רשימת אנשי קשר</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Névjegylista</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Lista de contacto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Elenco dei contatti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">კონტაქტების სია</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Kontaktu saraksts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Contactenlijst</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Spis kontaktów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Lista de contatos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zoznam kontaktov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Seznam stikov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Kontaktlista</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kişi Listesi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Список контактів</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxContact listxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">聯絡人列表</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/merkuro/calendar-week.png</image>
      <caption>Week View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الأسبوع</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Седмичен изглед</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Týdenní pohled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Ugevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Wochenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Week View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Semajna Vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista semanal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Asteko ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Viikkonäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en semaines</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista semanal.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת שבוע</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Heti nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista per septimana</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan Pekan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista settimanale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">კვირის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">주간 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Nedēļas skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Weekweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok tygodnia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização por semana</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie týždňa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Tedenski pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Veckovisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Hafta Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд тижня</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxWeek Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">單週檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/schedule_view.png</image>
      <caption>Schedule View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الجدولة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Изглед на график</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la planificació</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la planificació</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na plánování</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Tidsplansvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Terminplanansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Schedule View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Horaro Vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de planificación</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Plangintza ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Aikataulunäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en calendrier</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de programa.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת לו״ז</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Ütemezés nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Planification</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan Jadwal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle pianificazioni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">განრიგის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">일정 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Plānotāja skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Planningsweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok harmonogramu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização da agenda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie rozvrhu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled razporeda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Schemavisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Plan Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxSchedule Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">行程檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/task_view.png</image>
      <caption>Task View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض المهام</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Изглед със задачи</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de tasques</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de tasques</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na úlohy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Opgavevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Aufgabenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Task View</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Taska Vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de tareas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Zeregin ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tehtävänäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage en tâches</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Visor das tarefas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת משימות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Feladatnézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Carga</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan Tugas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle attività</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">დავალების ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">작업 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Uzdevumu skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Taakweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok zadań</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização de tarefa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Pohľad úloh</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled nalog</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Uppgiftsvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Görev Görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд завдання</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTask Viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">工作檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/mobile_view.png</image>
      <caption>Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">المحمول</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Мобилен</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Mobilní</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Mobil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Mobil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Poŝtelefono</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Dispositivo móvil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Mugikorra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Mobiili</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Móbil.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">נייד</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Mobil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Ponsel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მობილური</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">모바일</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Viedierīcē</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Mobiel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Pzenośny</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Celular</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Mobil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Mobilno</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Mobil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Taşınabilir Aygıt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мобільний</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMobilexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">行動版</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>merkuro-calendar</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/merkuro.calendar/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/pim/merkuro/-/issues</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24"/>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20"/>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05"/>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08"/>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03"/>
    <release version="22.08.2" date="2022-10-13"/>
    <release version="22.08.1" date="2022-09-08"/>
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#merkuro:kde.org</value>
    <value key="KDE::mastodon">https://kde.social/@merkuro</value>
    <value key="KDE::supporters">manchicken;Nithanim</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.merkuro.calendar.desktop</launchable>
</component>
